sainsburysentertainment.co.uk 2012-11-02

# Sainsbury's Entertainment | Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

**[www.sainsburys.co.uk/entertainment](http://www.sainsburysentertainment.co.uk/) is a site operated by Sainsbury’s Guernsey PCC Limited (we, us, our)** registered in Guernsey under company number 52041 and with our registered office and main trading address at Anson Court, La Route des Camps St Martin Guernsey GY4 6AD. 

Sainsbury’s Guernsey PCC Limited is committed to safeguarding your privacy. We believe that the best way to protect the privacy of users of [www.sainsburysentertainment.co.uk](http://www.sainsburysentertainment.co.uk/) and any other Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd controlled website (each a "Website") is to tell you what information we gather and ensure that you understand and consent to Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Limited’s uses of information you provide. We may occasionally modify the Privacy Policy and will post the revised Privacy Policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we use or disclose it. We may let you know via the homepage when this happens but you should check the policy frequently to read the latest Privacy Policy. Please note that the Website contains links to and from other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites whether or not we provide you with a link from this Website to such third party Websites. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those other websites. We set out below the answers to frequently asked questions regarding Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd’s Privacy Policy. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

We will only use your information for the purposes set out below if you have indicated that you wish us to use your information in this way when submitting the information. If at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the purposes detailed below you will need to go to the "Notifications" section within the "My Account" area and remove the tick from the relevant boxes.

• **Information you give us** : we receive and store any information you enter on our website or that you give us in any other way. You do not have to provide all of the information requested but that may mean that you cannot use the features of our website. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customising future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.  
• **Automatic information** : we receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the website or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd on other Web sites.  
• **E-mail communications** : to help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please ensure that you have unchecked the relevant boxes in the "Notifications" section within the "My Account" area.  
• **Information from other sources** : we might receive information abut you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

This information is stored on our database. Subject to the uses of this information to which you have consented, the database enables Sainsbury’s Guernsey PCC Ltd to provide you with information you request from us. We may also use your personal information to track activity on the Website. We do this in order to serve you better as we understand how you and other visitors use the Website. When we collect personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

We will only use your information for the purposes set out below if you have indicated that you wish us to use your information in this way when submitting the information. Additionally, if at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the below purposes, please let us know by contacting us through the "Contact Us" link on the Website or by emailing: [onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk](mailto:onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk).

We will stop the use of your information for such purposes as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so. 

We also use technology that allows us to track visitors to the Website so that we can understand how you and other visitors use it. For example, we use this technology to gather the following statistics: 

• your total number of visits;  
• your total number of page views;  
• how many pages you clicked on;  
• your location;  
• the length of time you spent on the Website;  
• where you arrived from (either directly, via a referring site or search engine);  
• your connection speed;  
• what browser/operating system/screen resolution you have.

**Security**

We are committed to using our best efforts to maintaining the security of your personal information and we do this in a number of ways: 

• we work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.   
• we reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.  
• we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer. 

Although we use our best efforts to protect the security of your personal information and our system, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, no transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of this and other factors beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit to or through our Website. Therefore, you assume that risk by using the Website. 

**Notice to minors**

This Site is intended for use by adults. If you are under **18** please do not send us any personal information including your email details. If you would like to contact us please do so through a parent or legal guardian (ask them to email us on your behalf). If you are a parent or legal guardian of a minor who has submitted us with personal information, please let us know by contacting us by clicking the "Contact Us" link on the Website or by emailing [onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk](mailto:%20onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk). We will delete such personally identifiable information from our database as soon as possible following our receipt of any such notice.

**Access to your information**

Where required under local law, we will, upon request and payment of any fee stipulated by local law, provide you with all the information we hold about you and which we are obliged to disclose to you. In making this request, please contact the Sainsbury’s Entertainment team ([onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk](mailto:%20onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk)) and specify that you require disclosure of your personal information.

**Do we share the information we receive?**

In addition to the sharing of your information as otherwise set forth in this policy, as Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd is part of a larger group your information may be shared between Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd group companies, a list of which can be obtained by contacting [onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk](mailto:%20onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk). Save as described below, we do not otherwise disclose information about your individual visits to the Website or information which identifies you to any third parties unless we have your prior consent or unless requested by local regulators and law enforcement officers or required by applicable law, rule or regulation. However, in order to provide an efficient service, certain functions such as hosting, storage fulfillment and disaster recovery are provided by third parties. Where this is the case we will ask those with whom we share data to agree to protect data as Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd has agreed in this Privacy Policy.

**Your Choice**

Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd permits you to opt-in to receive certain communications from us. If at any time you want to opt-out of receiving communications from Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd or that you no longer wish your feedback to be displayed on the Website, please let us know by contacting us at [onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk](mailto:onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk) and we will change your Preferences.

**Are there any security issues?**

We take the security of your data seriously. Therefore, once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

It is our policy to virus check documents and files before they are posted on this Website. However, we cannot guarantee that documents or files downloaded from this Website will be free from viruses and we do not accept any responsibility for any damage or loss caused by any virus. Accordingly, for your own protection, you must use virus-checking software when using this Website. You must not post or provide to us via this Website, any document or file which you believe may contain a virus. You must virus check any document or file which you intend to post or provide to us via this Website. 

Unfortunately no data transmission or security program can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. You remain responsible for the security of your computer at all times.

**Worldwide transfer of your data**

The dynamics of the Internet may mean that information is sent electronically outside of the country where you originally entered the information. In addition, that information may be used, stored and processed outside the country where you entered that information. While there is a risk that countries to which information is transferred will not be subject to an information protection regime as rigorous as that of the EEA or the United States as applicable, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and adequately protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, if you are resident in the EEA and you do not want your information to be transferred outside of the EEA please do not send us personal data. If you are a resident in the United States and do not want your information to be transferred outside of the United States please do not provide us with any information.

**What about ‘cookies’?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard-drive. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. We only use cookies to keep track of the pages you visit on the Website and to tell us whether you have visited the Website previously so that, in order to serve you better, we understand how you and other visitors use the Website. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. We have sought to set up our Website so as to notify you before a cookie is used. However, if you choose to reject all cookies, you may be unable to use parts of the Website. 

To view our Cookie Policy, please click  here.

**Your Consent**

You represent and warrant that all information you provide to us shall be truthful and accurate and shall not violate the rights of any third party. By using the Website and submitting information, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by us as described above and the transfer of your personal information to countries outside of the EEA or the United States as applicable.

**Accuracy of Your Personal Information**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the information you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

**Merger**

If Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd or Sainsburys Stores Ltd merges with, acquires or is sold to another company or goes into bankruptcy or engages in other such business transactions, we may share files and email records with our business and merger partners.

**Online data**

This general Privacy Policy only applies to the collection of data online and not to offline information. This Privacy Policy may be amended or superseded by a specific privacy policy for the collection and use of other data. Where this Privacy Policy is amended or superseded for the collection and use of other data Sainsbury’s Supermarkets Ltd will draw that amended privacy policy to your attention.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of England.

**Further Information**

If you have any requests or questions regarding this Privacy Policy please write to Sainsbury's Guernsey PCC Ltd at PO Box 336, Anson Court, La Route des Camps, St Martin, Guernsey, GY1 3UQ or contact us by e-mail using the following address: [onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk ](mailto:onlineservice@sainsburys.co.uk)
